Trevor Achtermann Fort Collins, Colorado

trevor.achtermann@outlook.com - 720.308.5251

www.linkedin.com/in/trevorachtermann wavsvn.github.io/lockeddoor

Currently a student in a Cyber Defense Training Program with @Level_Effect. Continuing to gain practical experience in network analysis, threat hunting, malware, digital forensics and front end development frameworks and fundamentals. Im largely self-taught and new to cyber in a professional degree, however, I possess and am willing to prove practical knowledge that I have found to be useful so far in my training program through a deep interest in computers from a young age and troubleshooting/exploiting various personal systems.

I have knowledge and skills pertaining to:

- > Network traffic analysis
- > Network vulnerability assessments
- > Windows and Linux systems
- > Windows Domains and Active Directory
- > Triage of Windows endpoints with Sysinternals
- > Familiarity with red team tools and tactics such as privilege escalation, persistence, and lateral movement through a network
- > Network infrastructure creation / setup
- > MIDI protocol use over a network
- > OSC protocol use over a network

- > MITRE ATT&CK Framework
- > Binary analysis
- > Utilizing SIEMs to monitor logging and alerts
- > Intrusion Detection/Prevention Systems
- > Log aggregation and analysis tools like ELK, Zeek, Snort, and Wireshark
- > Collecting digital evidence for clear communication of findings
- > Software and front end interface design
- > Back end web development
- > Front end web development
- > Private / public audio infrastructure setup
- > Live sound engineering

Work experience:

Jul 2022 - Jan 2023

Colorado Mesa University, Front End Developer Contract (non-student at this time)

- Worked as a contractor for CMU to design and build a simple informational website explaining different courses that comprised the graphic design bachelors program.
- set up and managed back end services that allowed the site's hosting and domain to function and connect properly.
- All work was done from scratch with the client stipulation of using a builder so the site can be modified easily. Project was cut short for unknown reasons, but I finished it unpaid and the domain is still valid for some reason. It takes a bit to load.
- you can see this site (assuming its still up) here: cmudesign.com

Work experience continued:

Mar 2020 - CURRENT

DoorDash, Driver \ Beta Tester

- Worked as a driver for doordash since early 2020 to make ends meet.
- 4.7 average rating over last 500 deliveries, 99% completion rate, 97% on time.
- Qualified for the beta-testing team for the dasher application, provided various bug reports to help imprive overall app experience for all contractors.

Feb 2023 - CURRENT

Self-Employed, Production \ Live Experience Trainer

- Using knowledge from my own musical pursuits and after building a fully networked personal solution for current and future live events of my own, I have been renting out both my time and pieces of old gear to interested residents in my local area who want to get into various parts of the music industry that I feel proficient enough to guide newcomers in.
- Most people want to learn how to dj, so thats the majority of what gets taught, but after learning djing to a certain degree of fluency many have continued bookings to learn more about the music production side of the industry and many start projects of their own.
- My personal project is roughly 5 years running and has taken a percieved pause as I focus on getting CDCP certified and the training program, but it continues to develop in the background.

Education:

College \ Colorado Mesa University

- 7/8 completed semesters of the Graphic Design Bachelors Program.
- I didnt complete the program due to medical complications that have since been resolved, however, during that period I realized design wasn't a career path that I thought would allow me to do anything I really cared about, alongside the fact much of the consumer design industry is leaning toward automation, and while I dont think automation will replace workers completely in any industry, I think I would more effective using automation as a tool for cyber work than I would be using it for design work.

High School \ Monarch High School

• Graduated May 2018.

Training and certifications:

- Eagle Scout.
- (in progress) Level Effect Cyber Defense Certified Professional [CDCP]